Pung Kah Jyun | Mobile No.: +65 96254652 | Email: kahjyun@hotmail.com |

LinkedIn: Pung KahJyun | LinkedIn

Objective

To be able to socialize by frequently working with, communicating with, and learning from systems/people. Solution-driven individual. Would enjoy utilizing my analytical and social skills in driving the attainment of business goals. Aspire to be a professional worker, to be involved in or be part of a management team; after working for several years in the industry. Seeking for any kind of challenges, as to broaden my job knowledge.

INTERNSHIP EXPERIENCE

United Overseas Bank Thailand

HR Student Intern

"Deployed to three HR functions (Talent & Dev/HRBP/Recruitment)"

Jun 2019 - Aug 2019

- Analyse and find insights in Employees' Engagement Survey
- Suggest improvements to UOBT's Handbook
- Update headcount of various employees in different functions
- Designed communication plans
 - *Letter of recommendation included*

Nanyang Polytechnic Singapore

HR Student Intern

"Recruitment Agency" Feb 2019 – Jun 2019

- Planned Recruitment Drive for Nanyang Polytechnic
- Conduct Interviews with Potential Candidates
- Created On Job Training (OJT)
- Design and post Job Posters

WORK EXPERIENCE

Grab Singapore Admin + Customer Service Apr 2020 – Jul 2020

Handled administrative duties such as data entries and updating into the system (Profile, Insurance checking)

- Customer services such as attending to drivers' queries and feedback
- Any other ad hoc admin & customer service duties

PartyMojo Pte Ltd Singapore

Part-Time Live Food Station Server

Sep 2019 - Mar 2020

- Set up & Clean-up of Machines (Popcorn, Candy Floss, others)
- Served food at specific food stations during service times
- Helped guests with a cheerful disposition

Education

National University of Singapore Degree in Information Systems (School of Computing)

Singapore Aug 2022 - Present

Participated in Hackathons: (Ideate Challenge, Lion City Hacks)

Tarticipated in Flackathoris. (Ideate Challenge, Elon Oity Flacks)

Nanyang Polytechnic Singapore

Diploma in Business Management (Human Resources + International Business)

Apr 2017 - May 2020

- CGPA: 3.78/4
- Director's List Academic Achievement Award recipient [4 out of 6 semesters]
- CCA: Executive Team Senior Member

Chung Cheng High (Yishun)

Singapore

As in Maths and Science for N & O Levels

Jan 2010 - Dec 2016

- CCA: Running Club Chairman (2013 2015)
- CCA: Outdoor Activities Club Vice Chairman (2015 2016)

Technical Expertise

Proficient in Microsoft Word, PowerPoint, and Excel Familiar with HTML, CSS, Python, Java, Tableau

Possess good leadership, management, and verbal communication skills

Bilingual - English & Mandarin

Certifications/Awards

Engineering Mathematics – Calculus	May 2022 - Aug 2022
Scientific Computing with Python (freeCodeCamp)	Feb 2022
https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/KahJyun/scientific-computing-with-python-v7	
Data Analytics Using Excel (Nanyang Polytechnic)	Mar 2022
Platoon Best Award (Sergeant Cadet School)	Nov 2020
Director's List Academic Achievement Award recipient [4 out of 6 semesters]	2017 – 2020
SBM Executive Team Recognition	2017 – 2019
Participation in Industry Digitalisation Masterclass	2017
MOE Scholarships Award	2012
MOE Good Progress Award	2011 & 2015

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

Volunteering

Foochow Methodist Church Missionary Trip to Indonesia Volunteer Leader

Indonesia

Dec 2019

- In charge of organizing games and camp activities for 30 children to encourage interaction with one another.
- Communicated with Indonesians with different cultures and lifestyles and develop multicultural sensitivity and appreciation of diverse cultures.

Singapore Salvation Army Assembling Staff

Singapore 2020

Allocated unused and used appliances to their respective locations

Coordinated with permanent staff on procedures to be followed in the collection, distribution, and filling/retrieving of the items

Coding

GitHub: Fastumkj's gists (github.com)

Anime

Mobile Games

Learning new languages